

LALU ALIYYA TIRANGGA AJI **BUANA**

Magister Student

- Kaliurang st. no 23, Karangwuni Sleman, Yogyakarta, Indonesia
- ☑ aliyyatirangga03@gmail.com
- **&** +62-859-4077-4947

SOCIAL

- in @lalualiyyatirangga
- @lalualiyyatirangga
- @ @lalualiyyatirangga

PORTFOLIO



iii @lalualiyyatirangga

PROFILE

M.Eng student in Geological Engineering, Geographic Information System (GIS) & Remote Sensing (RS) enthusiast. Currently, he is an active member of multiple GIS & RS-related societies. Master's student with several internship experience in mapping survey and WebGIS development.

EDUCATION

MASTER OF GEOLOGICAL **ENGINEERING**

Universitas Gadjah Mada 2020 - Present

BACHELOR OF GEOLOGICAL **ENGINEERING**

Universitas Gadjah Mada 2015 - 2019

SKILLS

- Geologic &
- Drone Mapping
- GIS & Remote
- Sensing
 - Geographic
- Data Collection
- Groundwater Modelling

- Python
- SQL
- HTML
- **CSS**
- Javascript

INTERESTS

GIS & RS

 \boxtimes

Hydrogeology

Geophysics

GIS Developer

EXPERIENCE

GIS Analyst

analysis.

January 2020 - March 2020 | PT. Braga Teknologi Nusantara

An internship programme after graduation with responsible for developing a simple WebGIS regards to education facilities in Jakarta.

July 2020 - September 2020 | Dinas Perumahan & Pemukiman LOTENG An internship programme after graduation with responsible for field

survey, geographic mapping data collection, drone mapping, & GIS

Field Assistant

August 2019 - October 2019 | Pusat Kajian LKFT UGM

Working as student intern with several tasks such as preliminary survey & digital map production.

Field Assistant

May 2019 - July 2019 | PT. Amman Mineral Nusa Tenggara

Working as student intern with several tasks such as water piezometric data collection & analysis in Batu Hijau Open Pit, West Sumbawa, Indonesia.

HONORS AND AWARDS

Best Student Prize of ExploreSA: The Gawler Challenge (September 2020)

A global online competition to identify or predict areas of potential mineralization within the Gawler region from the Government of South Australia with over 2000+ registered participant from 100+ countries.

Paper Presentation on The 2019 International Conference on Climate Change, Disaster Management, and Environmental Sustainability (September 2019)

An international scientific conference opens for all professionals and students held by Kumamoto University, Japan

1st Winner of Eco-City: Design Your Future (April 2019)

A global competition opens for worldwide students to share the ideas related to Eco-City Issues, held by University of Malaya, Malaysia.

Best Paper of The 16th Hokkaido Indonesian Student Association Scientific Meeting (March 2019)

An international scientific meeting and paper competition opens for all students held by PPI Hokkaido.

3rd Winner of Lomba Geospasial Inovatif Nasional (February 2019)

A national competition to the ideas and innovation related to geospatial issues in Indonesia, held by Geodetic Engineering Department, Universitas Gadjah Mada, Indonesia.

REFERENCES

Saptono Budi Samodra, S.T., M.Sc.

Email: Sbsamodra@ugm.ac.id

LANGUAGES

Supardi, M.T., IPM

Email: Supardi@amnt.co.id

Indonesian English